Hey, you guys. Hey, what are you doing?
嗨  你俩在干什么
Figuring out our wedding plans.
筹备婚礼
Funny. We were doing the same thing.
太巧了  我们也正合计这事呢
It's really crazy. The hall, the dress, the food.
疯了  场地  服装  食品
I had no idea how expensive this was.
没想到结个婚这么贵
Yeah, it is really pricey.
是很贵
I freaked when I heard the numbers.
第一次算出结婚费用  我被那个数字吓呆了
So, what did you two do about it?
结果你们怎么做的
It was simple.
简单
I came up with some cost-cutting solutions...
我想出了一些省钱方案
...wrote out a list, and Monica told me to go to hell.
列了个清单  结果莫妮卡叫我去死
There's no way around it.
没钱好省的
Just accept that this is gonna cost a lot of money.
只能接受现实  确实会花很多钱
I heard that weddings are, like, a $40 billion-a-year industry.
听说每年花在结婚上的钱高达400亿
Yeah. And I'm responsible for just, like, half of that.
这其中我贡献过半
But really, it does seem like this money could be put to better use.
我觉得这钱应该用在更有意义的事上
Are you serious?
当真
Yeah. How would you feel
把婚礼经费
if we gave all the wedding money to charity...
捐献给慈善事业
...and we just got married at City Hall?
我们就到市政厅登个记  如何
I think it would make me wanna marry you even more.
这让我越发想娶你了
I gotta say, you guys, that's an incredible gesture.
不得不说  你们的高姿态  很好
Maybe you do that next time you get married.
下次你结婚也这么干如何
No, no, no. The next time's gonna be Hawaii at sunset.
不不不  下次我要在夏威夷斜阳下结婚
But maybe the time after that.
不过下下次可以听取你的意见
《老友记》第十季第七集  领养中心来家访
《老友记》  第十季  第7集  领养中心来家访
- Hey. What's going on? - Hey.
-嘿  忙啥呢  -嘿
Our adoption social worker is coming,
领养中心有人来家访
so we're cleaning the apartment.
所以我们在扫除
"We"?
我们
You know you don't want me to help.
你不想我掺和
You can't have it both ways.
别现在又说这个
Is this the person who decides
这个人能决定
whether or not you get a baby?
你们是否收养一个孩子
Kind of. She's coming by to interview us and see where we live.
差不多  这人来视察我们的生活环境
And it has to go perfectly,
我们必须表现得完美
because if she doesn't like something about us
若她对我们有丝毫不满
she can keep us off
她就会让我们进不了
every adoption list in the state.
全国任何一个领养的名单里
Hey, maybe I should stop by.
我可以过来友情协力一把
She could be a soap opera fan.
她没准爱看肥皂剧
It's very impressive
小人物认识演艺名流
when the little people know a celebrity.
可以蓬壁生辉呢
"Little people"?
小人物
"Celebrity."
名流
So I think I'm just about done here.
我觉得我做的差不多了
Unless you have any bad stuff hidden somewhere,
除非你还在哪
like porn or cigarettes?
藏了像黄书  香烟什么的
What?
什么
- No. - Chandler.
-才没有  -钱德勒
I don't,
我没有
and I'm offended by the insinuation.
这样玷污人家清白太气人了
So there's not a magazine under the couch...
沙发下没有杂志
...or cigarettes taped to the back of the toilet tank...
厕所水箱后没有一包香烟
...or a filthy video in the VCR?
录象机里没有A片
I'll admit to the cigarettes and magazine.
香烟和杂志我认帐
But that tape is not mine.
但带子不是我的
It isn't mine.
也不是我的
I guess we'll never know whose it is.
我想我们永远不会知道是谁的了
May I help you?
可以帮忙吗
Yes. We're here
我们来给孩子们
to make a rather sizable donation to the children.
捐一大笔钱
Any contribution, large or small,
捐钱不论多少  心意都是一样重
is appreciated.
我们都会感激
I think you're gonna appreciate
数目这样大
the crap out of this one.
你一定会把屎都感动出来了
Well, this is very generous.
你们真大方
And we don't want any recognition.
我们要匿名捐助
This is completely anonymous.
完全匿名
Completely anonymous. From two kind strangers.
完全匿名  就写两个陌生人
Mr. X and Phoebe Buffay.
先生甲和菲比·布菲
Well if you like,
如果你们愿意
we can include your names in our newsletter.
我们可以把二位的名字登到新闻通讯里
Not necessary.
没必要
Buffay is spelled B-U-F-F-A-Y.
布菲的拼法是  B-U-F-F-A-Y
And X is spelled "Mike Hannigan."
先生甲的写法是  迈克·汉尼根
Well, on behalf of the children, thank you both very much.
我代表孩子们多谢两位
I'm glad we did this. It feels so good.
我很高兴我们这么做了  感觉真棒
It does. It feels really good.
是啊  非常棒
Oh, look. And we get these free T-shirts.
还有免费T恤拿
Actually, that's the shirt I wore to the gym.
那是我健身穿的
It's moist.
难怪是湿的
Hi. Emma will be up in a minute.
艾玛会很快起床的
Oh, good.
好啊
Hey, Ross, listen. I heard about you and Charlie.
嘿  罗斯  听说你跟查莉的事了
I'm really sorry.
替你难过
That's okay.
没事
I'm sure there are tons of other beautiful paleontologists out there.
美貌的考古学家多的是
Absolutely.
当然
There was one. She's it.
只有一个  就是她
All the rest look like they should live under a bridge.
其他的就好象是桥洞居民一样
So, what are you gonna do today?
今天想怎么玩
I was thinking of taking Emma to the playground.
带艾玛去街心游乐场怎么样
Oh, my God. What?
天啊  什么
Like I said, I was thinking of
我又没说
taking Emma to the Museum of Knives and Fire.
带她去武器弹药博物馆
Okay, look, Ross.
听着  罗斯
I do not want Emma going to the playground.
我反对艾玛去游乐场
Because...?
因为
All right, if you must know, I had a traumatic...
好吧  如果你想知道…
...swing incident when I was little.
我小时候荡秋千遇险
- Seriously? - Yes. I was 4 years old.
-真的  -我才四岁
And I was on the swing...
我荡秋千
...and then all of a sudden my hair got tangled in the chain.
突然头发缠到铁链上
And to get me out,
结果老妈剪掉我一大缕头发
my mom had to cut a big chunk of my hair.
才救我出来
And it was uneven for weeks.
结果有好几星期头发才长齐
And you made it through that?
你竟熬了过来
I wonder who's gonna play you in the movie.
简直可以拍成电影
Okay, fine, you can make fun of me.
你尽管拿我取笑
I do not want Emma going there.
反正我就是不想艾玛去
Claire Danes:美剧《国家安全》女主角
我在想能不能让克莱尔·丹妮丝扮演我
Look, I'm sorry to hear about your tragedy.
你的悲剧令我同情
But the swings are perfectly safe.
不过秋千很安全
And besides, Emma loves them.
而且艾玛喜欢荡秋千
You should come, and you'll see.
我们同去  你就知道了
Those things go, like, 40 miles an hour.
秋千速度高达40英里/小时
And there's that moment when you're at the top...
当你荡到最高处
...when you just don't know if you're gonna return back to Earth.
鬼才知道会不会返回地球
Space is filled with orbiting children.
宇宙充满小孩子绕轨道运行
Look, please, just come on.
求你了  来嘛
When you see the look on Emma's face,
你若看见艾玛的小表情
I swear, you won't regret it.
决不会后悔
- All right. - Good.
-好吧  -太好了
You don't wanna be a mom
你不会像有的妈妈那样
who passes her irrational fears to her children.
把自己失去理智的恐惧遗传给小孩吧
"Irrational," huh?
"失去理智"
I'll remember that next time
下次你被家里的蜘蛛吓到
you freak out about a spider in your apartment.
我们再谈这个话题
That's the same. I'm sure there are 30
这两个可以相提并论吗  秋千上
different species of poisonous swings.
有30种不同毒液
Oh, my God. The adoption lady is early.
天啊  领养中心的来早了
Okay. Okay. Here we go. Here we go.
好的好的  镇静镇静
Stand up straight.
站直咯
Big smile.
微笑
Hello. Is this the Creepy residence?
你们好  请问这是"毛骨悚然"家吗
We're waiting for the adoption lady.
还以为是领养中心的来了
But I'm glad you're here.
你来得正好
I was cleaning this morning
今早打扫时发现的
and I found this.
不知道你用不用得上
I don't know if you wanna use it, but....
我不知道你是不是想用  但是...
Oh, this is so sweet of you.
你真好
But you know what?
但是你知道吗
I won't be needing a veil,
我并不需要这头纱
I actually won't be wearing a dress at all!
我实际上都不会穿婚纱
I told you,
我告诉过你
I am not coming to a naked wedding!
裸体婚礼我不会参加的
No. We're not having a big reception.
我们不会招待宴请
we took the money we were gonna spend on a wedding
我们把婚礼经费
and we donate them to the children charity.
捐给儿童慈善事业了
That's crazy!
你真疯狂
I'm sorry. I can't imagine giving up
抱歉  只是无法想象
my one wedding day like that.
一生只有一次啊
Well, we're different.
我们不同
I don't care about having a huge party.
我不在乎什么盛大婚礼
This is really nice for you, but....
头纱你戴是很美  但是...
Oh, please. I put this on and I just look like--
你看我一戴上  简直就...
Well, radiant.
美极了
All right, but who cares?
管它呢
I don't need a pretty veil and a fancy dress.
我不需要头纱婚纱这些玩意
That's right. You're making a commitment.
对  你们是互许终身
You know, that's the same whether you do it at the Plaza or....
不管在广场举行还是别的什么地方都是一样
- Where you gonna do it? - City Hall.
-你选了啥地方  -市政厅
Oh, that sounds nice.
好地方
I was just there for jury duty.
我刚去过那做评审委员
They've really spruced that place up.
他们把那打理得非常整洁漂亮呢
Okay. It's okay...
没关系...
I've made my decision.
我已经下定决心
What I really want is a great big wedding.
但我真正想要的是一个盛大的婚礼
But you gave all the money to charity.
但钱已经捐啦
Well, I'll just ask for it back.
可以要回来
I don't think you can do that.
不行吧
Why not?
怎么不行
This is her wedding day.
她这可是结婚
That's way more important than some stupid kids.
这可比什么愚蠢的小孩子重要多了
That's sweet, honey,
说得好  亲爱的
but save something for the adoption lady.
但这些话省下来说给领养中心的人听吧
- All right, okay. Be careful. - Okay.
-好  小心点  -好
Careful. Watch her hair. Watch her hair!
小心  小心她头发
Rach, she's got, like, three hairs.
她才三根毛
I know. I know.
我知道  我知道
But they're just so beautiful.
但是很漂亮
Oh, my God, I just pulled one out.
糟糕  扯掉一根
I promise you she's safe.
我保证  她很安全
Watch how much she loves this.
你看她多喜欢玩秋千
Okay. Okay.
好吧  好吧
Are you ready, sweetie? Here we go.
你准备好了吗  亲爱的  开始喽
Okay, careful. Okay.
小心
She's smiling.
她笑了
Look at that, she does like it.
看  她真的很喜欢
See, I told you.
看到没  我告诉过你的吧
Oh, my God.
天啊
Look at her, she's a little daredevil.
看看她真有不怕死的精神
Oh, God. Let me push. Can I push?
让我推好不好
Oh, absolutely.
哦  当然
Oh, God. Okay, get the camera.
你去拿相机
It's in the diaper bag.
在尿布包里
Okay.
好
See? Scared of the swings.
还怕秋千
I bet you feel pretty silly.
现在觉得傻了吧
We're asking for the money back?
我们真要把钱要回来
It's for our wedding day.
结婚要用
Now, is this guy gay or straight?
这小子喜欢男的女的
Because one of us has to start flirting.
我们非得出美人计
You here to make another donation the same day?
你们一天来捐两次钱
I don't think that's ever happened before.
真是前所未有呢
Gay. Go.
同性恋  你上
Oh, my God, I love your shirt.
天呐  你的衬衣好帅
The donation we made earlier?
我们今天捐的钱
Well, we want it back.
我们想要回来
Excuse me?
什么
Okay, that money was for a big wedding
那是办婚礼的钱
we thought we didn't want.
我们本来不想大办
But it turns out we do.
但现在我们改变了主意
So you're asking us
所以你要我们退还
to refund your donation to the children?
你们捐给孩子们的钱
Yeah.
对
This feels really good.
这样感觉真不错
I'm sorry. I am.
对不起  真的
But this wedding's just really important to me.
但婚礼对我相当重要
Hey, it's none of my business.
不关我事
Besides, this is probably a good thing.
也许这是件好事
We've really been spoiling the children,
别把孩子惯坏了
what with all the food and warm clothing.
让他们吃饱穿暖干嘛
That's not fair.
你这么说不公平
A person's wedding is important.
结婚是大事
And especially to me.
尤其对于我来说
I didn't have a graduation party.
我没参加过毕业典礼
And I didn't go to prom.
没有毕业舞会
And I spent my sweet 16 being chased around a tire yard...
在我的16岁生日的时候
...by an escaped mental patient
我被精神病人在一个废旧轮胎场地狂追
who, in his own words, wanted to:
他还说
"Kill me, or whatever."
杀我什么的
So I deserve a real celebration.
我应当有个隆重的婚礼
And I'm not gonna let some sweaty little man
我不会让你个流汗男
make me feel badly about it.
弄的我觉得内疚
She could've been talking about either one of us.
她也有可能是在说我
Hi, I'm Laura.
我是劳拉
I'm here for your adoption interview.
我来做领养家访
Hi, I'm Monica. And this is Chandler.
我是莫妮卡  这是钱德勒
- Please come in. - Thank you.
-请进  -谢谢
Would you like something to drink?
请进  喝点什么
Water would be fine.
喝水可以了
We're so glad that you're here.
你总算来了
We're excited about getting this process started.
我们好兴奋  终于开始领养小孩的流程了
Because we love kids. Love them to death.
因为我们爱小孩  爱得要死
Well, not actually to death.
不是真的要孩子"死"
That's just a figure of speech.
只是这么形容一下
We love kids the appropriate amount...
我们爱孩子  恰当合理
...as allowed by law.
符合法律法规
- Your place is just lovely. - Thank you.
-你们家好可爱  -谢谢
Yes, this building does have a wholesome,
这栋楼的确看起来很卫生
family feel to it.
给人家的感觉
I feel like I've been here before.
我好像来过这里
Any other couples in the building adopting?
这里还有谁家在申请领养吗
Is that that couple on the first floor?
是不是一楼那家
Because we should get a baby before them.
我们应该比他们先得到孩子
That guy tried to sell me drugs.
他还想卖毒品给我
But other than that,
但其他人都好
wholesome, wholesome building.
这是栋干净卫生的楼
What?
怎么
I realized why I remember this place.
我想起来了为什么我对这楼有记忆了
Really? What is it?
真的  怎么回事
Oh, it's nothing.
哦  没什么
I went on a date with a guy who lived in this building.
我和住在这栋楼里的一个男人约会
It didn't end very well.
结果无疾而终
That wouldn't, by any chance, be Joey Tribbiani?
那人该不是叫乔伊·崔比安尼吧
- Yes! - Of course it was.
-就是他  -当然是他
We had a great night.
良宵过后
In the morning, he promised he'd call
他说他再打电话给我
and he didn't.
结果再没联络
Rat bastard!
真他妈混蛋
So you're not friends with him?
你们该不是他朋友
Oh, God, no.
当然不是  不
No. Nope.
当然不是
No...
不...
Well, I'm sorry I brought it up.
抱歉提到这事
So are either one of you planning on staying at home?
那么你们当中有人打算待在家里吗
Hello? Anybody in there order a celebrity?
有人吗  名人驾到
What was that?
怎么了
That's just some crazy guy who roams the halls here.
过道上乱跑的疯子
He's great with kids, though.
不过他对小孩很慈祥
Ross. Oh, my God, are you okay?
罗斯  天啊  你还好
Son of a bitch!
他妹的
Oh, relax. I didn't say the F-word.
别紧张  我又没说F打头那个字
Ross, see,
罗斯  看吧
I told you! Those swings are evil!
早告诉你了  秋千太邪恶了
That is it.
就这一次了
That's the last time Emma is getting on
这辈子再也不许
one of those things for her entire life.
艾玛接近它
No, no, no. Okay, it wasn't the swing's fault.
别这样  不是秋千的错
It was my fault.
是我错
And kind of that kid's fault.
还有那孩子的错
Who is still laughing. Nice.
他还笑呢  算你恨
Come on. Can we just get out of here
在再有人受伤之前
before somebody else gets hurt?
我们走吧
No. Wait. Ok, ok. I have an idea.
不  等等  这样吧
I want you to get on the swing...
你去荡秋千
...and you'll see that there's nothing to be afraid of.
你会发现没什么好担心的
I know what this is all about.
我知道你意欲何为了
You've always been jealous of my hair.
你一贯嫉妒我满头秀发
I just think you're an adult, okay?
这只是想你已经成年了
And you should get over your silly fears.
该克服那些愚蠢的恐惧了
All right, fine. I'll do it.
好  上就上
Good.
好
If you hold a spider.
如果你敢抓蜘蛛
Where?! Where?!
在哪儿  在哪儿
I know.
我听见了
Guys, is everything okay?
伙计们  没事吧
It's me, Joey.
是我  乔伊
Adoption!
领养
What's going on?
到底怎么回事
Oh, it's just like I said, that crazy...
就是那个叫波特疯子
...Bert, roaming the halls.
在过道上跑
Guys?
伙计们
Keep on roaming, Bert!
接着跑吧  波特
We don't want any crazy today!
今天我们不看你疯了
What's going on?
到底怎么了
We'll talk later! Bert. Everything's fine!
我们等会再说  波特  一切都好
Everything doesn't sound fine.
听起来就是有问题
Is he all right out there by himself?
他独自一个在外面  不会出事吧
Oh, yeah. He has a caretaker.
没事  他有监管人
His older brother...
是他哥
...Ernie.
叫欧尼
Bert and Ernie?
波特和欧尼
You can't make this stuff up.
无巧不成书
You never told me about that guy
你没说过你16岁生日时
and your sweet 16.
被男人追杀的故事
I'm sorry about that.
真可怜
Oh, it ended okay.
结局还算好
One of my friends shot him.
我朋友毙了他
At least you'll get a proper wedding.
至少你会有个体面婚礼
You really deserve that.
你该得的
Yeah, I really do.
是的  没错
You know, I had nothing growing up.
知道吗  长这么大我还没风光过
Just like the kids I took the money from.
就像被我剥夺金钱的那些孩子一样
No... I see where this is going.
不...  看出你苗头了
Don't make me go back there.
别又想让我退回去
Look, I can't have a wedding with this money now.
我不能用这钱办婚事
It's tainted.
这样就有污点了
Fine, we'll give the money back.
好吧  退回就是了
If that guy at the charity
如果慈善捐助处那家伙
gives us a hard time...
又叫咱们难看
...my friend hasn't shot anyone in a really long time.
我朋友的老枪好久没见过血了
I must say this seems like
我想说  这种环境
a lovely environment to raise a child in.
培养小孩似乎很理想
You are welcome to look under
你尽可以在各种家具
any of the furniture...
下面搜查
...because, believe me,
相信我
you won't find any porn or cigarettes under there.
绝无黄书和香烟什么的
Before we look around,
在到处看看之前
let me make sure
让我先检查下我的表
I have everything I need up to here.
是不是都填好了
Why don't I show you the baby's room.
我带你去看看婴儿房
What are you doing?
你干啥
You wouldn't let me in.
你不让我进来
I thought you were in trouble.
我以为你们出事了
Well, we're not.
才没有
But you called me "Bert."
但你叫我"波特"
That's our code word for danger.
那是"危险"的暗号
We don't have a code word.
我们没约定过什么暗号
We don't?
没有吗
We really should.
应该约一个
From now on,
从今往后
"Bert" will be our code word for danger.
"波特"就用来作为遇到危险的暗号
So that was the baby's room.
参观完婴儿房
What room should we see next?
下面参观哪里
Any room that isn't behind this couch.
除了沙发后面都可以参观
Some people don't get him,
有些人不懂他的笑话
but I think he's really funny.
但我觉得他真幽默
I did not care for that.
我不在乎被你粗暴对待
You have to leave.
你得回避
You slept with our social worker
你和这个社工睡过
and never called her back.
再没联络她
She is still pissed,
她还在生你的气
so she can't see you.
不能让她见到你
Okay, okay.
好  好
- What? - I forgot my bat.
-怎么了  -忘了拿球棒
Oh, my God.
天呐
And for the last time,
最后一次告诉你
we do not want to be friends with you!
我们不想和你做朋友
And we don't wanna buy your bat!
也不想买你的球棒
What are you doing here?
你来这儿干什么
Bert...
"波特"...
Are you friends with him?
你们是朋友
I can explain.
我来解释
Joey?
乔伊你说
All right. Okay.
好吧
You have got some nerve coming back here.
你还敢回来  太有种了
I can't believe you never called me.
真不敢相信你竟从来没给我打过电话
Excuse me?
你说什么呢
You probably don't even remember my name.
你可能连我名字也忘了吧
It's Joey, by the way.
告诉你  我叫乔伊
And don't bother telling me yours,
不必说你的名字
because I totally remember it, lady.
我记得  女士
I waited weeks for you to call me.
我一直等你电话
I gave you my number.
我给你电话号码了
You never called me.
你没联系我啊
Don't try to turn this around on me.
还想把屎盆子往我身上扣
I am not some kind of social work...
我可不是
...that you can just...
让你可以随便做的
...do.
社会工作
I'm pretty sure I gave you my number.
我确信给过你电话
Really? Think about it. Come on.
真的吗  那你想想看
You're a beautiful woman.
你这么漂亮
Smart, funny.
聪明又有趣
We had a really good time.
你我春风一度
If I had your number,
如果我有你电话
why wouldn't I call you?
怎么可能不打给你
I don't know.
就是不知道呀
Well, maybe I'm wrong.
可能我搞错了
I'm sorry.
对不起
Hey, too late for apologies. Okay?
现在道歉太晚啦
You broke my heart.
你伤了我的心
You know how many women
你知道就为了忘掉你
I had to sleep with to get over you?
我睡了多少女人吗
- Joey, wait-- - No!
-乔伊  留步... -不
I waited a long time!
我等得够久
I can't wait anymore.
不可能再等了
I'm sorry that you had to see that.
抱歉让你们笑话了
I'm so embarrassed.
太丢人了
Oh, that's really okay.
没事
Yeah. We totally understand.
我们理解
Dating is hard.
约会可够人受的
Boy, you people are nice.
你们真是好人
And I've got to say...
我得说…
...l think you're going to make excellent parents.
你们一定会是很棒的父母
Laura!
劳拉
We're back.
我们回来啦
Are you here to take more money?
你们是想再多要点钱
Because I think what you're looking for is an ATM.
你们应该找提款机
No, no, we're here to give the money back.
不不  我们把钱退给你们
Yeah. Because you know what?
因为你知道
It's all about the children.
一切都是为了孩子
Although it's also about the wedding.
当然  我们的婚礼也很重要
All right, here.
好吧  给
No. Oh, God.
不要  天呐
If I haven't said so already,
我好像还没有说
sir, congratulations.
恭喜你啊  先生
Enough, all right?
够了  好吗
I'm stepping in and putting my foot down.
我要插手做决定了
As your future husband,
作为你的未来老公
I'm gonna make this decision for us.
我说了算
What do you think we should do?
你说咋办
You know what. It's not your decision anymore.
现在不是你们说了算了
What?
什么
On behalf of the children of New York,
我代表纽约儿童
I reject your money.
拒绝你们的捐款
But we're giving you this.
但是我们在给你钱啊
And I'm giving it back to you.
现在退给你们
Come on. Consider it a contribution.
拿着吧  当作礼金好了
Well, this is very generous.
你可真够大方啊
Please take the check.
支票拿走
Have a great wedding
祝婚礼成功
and a wonderful life together.
幸福甜蜜
Sounds good to me.
听来不错
We can save up, come back in a few years...
我们以后存了钱
...and make an even bigger donation.
过两年捐更多
Absolutely. And when you do, make sure you ask for Brian.
当然  下次记得找布莱恩捐
- Oh, is that you? - No.
-布莱恩是你  -不
Hello?
喂
Oh, hi.
哦  嗨
Oh, my God, really?
天啊  真的吗
I can't wait to tell Chandler.
我迫不及待想告诉钱德勒了
Okay. Goodbye.
好  再见
Wrong number?
打错电话的
That was Laura.
是劳拉
She gave us a great report
她替我们大大美言
and we're officially on the waiting list.
我们正式上了领养排队名单
That's great.
太好了
Now we just wait for a call...
我们现在就等人
...and someone tells us
给我们打电话告诉我们
there's a baby waiting for us.
有个小孩等我们去领养了
Hello?
喂
Have you seen Joey's bat?
看见乔伊的球棒吗
Okay. I got a spider.
好了  我捉到了蜘蛛
There were two, I picked the bigger one.
有两只  我挑了只大的
- Okay. - Okay.
-好的  -好的
This feels perfectly normal.
感觉一切正常
Okay, get on the swing.
好了  你上秋千去
Okay.
好啊
See?
看到了吗
All right. I can do this.
啊  没事了  我可以玩秋千了
There you go. Good for you.
是啊  干得好
You know what? I'm getting used to this little guy.
知道吗  我已经习惯这小家伙了
I don't even feel him in here anymore.
我已经完全感觉不到它的存在了
That's because he's on your neck.
因为它爬到你脖子上去了